[Music]
[âm nhạc]
Spring is coming, a new year is about to begin,
xuân xuân đang về một năm mới sắp sang
children, study hard
các con trăm học
! There's a red gift box, green fruit, and a
nhé nà là hộp quà đỏ quả xanh nà là hộp
purple and gold gift box, the fairy godmother brings
quà trang tím vàng ông bụt mang đến tặng
gifts from Mom. Open the door, open the
làm quà của mẹ chai mở cánh cửa mở cánh
door! For the
cửa ra nào Cho ông bụt cho ông bụt thân
dear fairy godmother, welcome another
yêu Chào đón thêm một năm
new year! Open the door, open the door! Happy New Year!
mới mở cánh cửa mở cánh cửa ra nào chà n
Everything will be peaceful and
mơi chà nm mơi Sắp sáng mọi sự được an
joyful following the footsteps of Buddha. Open the door, welcome the
vui theo bước chân phật đà mở cánh cửa x
dear fairy godmother! Welcome another new year, a bright new year following the
yêu Chào đón thêm một năm mới sáp sáng
teachings of Buddha Shakyamuni.
theo chi giá Phật Thích Ca Mâu
Open the door,
Ni mở cnh cửa ra
welcome the dear fairy godmother!
nào chào đón ông mộtt thân
Welcome another new year, a bright new year following the
yêu Chào đón thêm một năm mới sáp sang
teachings of Buddha Shakyamuni!
theo chi giá Phật Thích Ca Mâu
Happy New Year! Happy New Year!
Ni Happy New Year Happy New Year Ngọc
Abundant happiness! Happy New Year, everything will be peaceful and
tràn niệm hạnh phúc Happy New Year mọi
joyful following the footsteps of Buddha. Happy New Year! Happy
sự an vui theo bước chân phật đà Happy
New Year! Joyful
New Year Happy New Year rộn ràng khắp
everywhere, welcoming the dear fairy godmother!
nơi chào đón ông buồn thân
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
1 2 3 Welcome the New Year! Happy New
1 2 3 chào đón năm mới Happy New
Year!
Year